{
  "1" : {
    "question" : "Add \\(\\frac {5} {7} + \\frac {2} {4}\\).",
    "answer" : "34/28",
    "solution" : "\\(\\frac {5} {7} + \\frac {2} {4} = \\frac {20} {28} + \\frac {14} {28} = \\frac {34} {28}\\).",
    "explanation" : ""
  },
  "2" : {
    "question" : "Add \\(\\frac {4} {8} + \\frac {2} {3}\\).",
    "answer" : "28/24",
    "solution" : "\\(\\frac {4} {8} + \\frac {2} {3} = \\frac {12} {24} + \\frac {16} {24} = \\frac {28} {24}\\).",
    "explanation" : ""
  },
  "3" : {
    "question" : "Add \\(\\frac {3} {4} + \\frac {3} {5}\\).",
    "answer" : "27/20",
    "solution" : "\\(\\frac {3} {4} + \\frac {3} {5} = \\frac {15} {20} + \\frac {12} {20} = \\frac {27} {20}\\).",
    "explanation" : ""
  },
  "4" : {
    "question" : "Add \\(\\frac {1} {3} + \\frac {4} {5}\\).",
    "answer" : "17/15",
    "solution" : "\\(\\frac {1} {3} + \\frac {4} {5} = \\frac {5} {15} + \\frac {12} {15} = \\frac {17} {15}\\).",
    "explanation" : ""
  },
  "5" : {
    "question" : "Add \\(\\frac {1} {6} + \\frac {5} {8}\\).",
    "answer" : "38/48",
    "solution" : "\\(\\frac {1} {6} + \\frac {5} {8} = \\frac {8} {48} + \\frac {30} {48} = \\frac {38} {48}\\).",
    "explanation" : ""
  },
  "6" : {
    "question" : "Add \\(\\frac {8} {9} + \\frac {2} {6}\\).",
    "answer" : "66/54",
    "solution" : "\\(\\frac {8} {9} + \\frac {2} {6} = \\frac {48} {54} + \\frac {18} {54} = \\frac {66} {54}\\).",
    "explanation" : ""
  },
  "7" : {
    "question" : "Add \\(\\frac {1} {4} + \\frac {2} {7}\\).",
    "answer" : "15/28",
    "solution" : "\\(\\frac {1} {4} + \\frac {2} {7} = \\frac {7} {28} + \\frac {8} {28} = \\frac {15} {28}\\).",
    "explanation" : ""
  },
  "8" : {
    "question" : "Add \\(\\frac {1} {9} + \\frac {4} {7}\\).",
    "answer" : "43/63",
    "solution" : "\\(\\frac {1} {9} + \\frac {4} {7} = \\frac {7} {63} + \\frac {36} {63} = \\frac {43} {63}\\).",
    "explanation" : ""
  },
  "9" : {
    "question" : "Add \\(\\frac {2} {4} + \\frac {2} {6}\\).",
    "answer" : "20/24",
    "solution" : "\\(\\frac {2} {4} + \\frac {2} {6} = \\frac {12} {24} + \\frac {8} {24} = \\frac {20} {24}\\).",
    "explanation" : ""
  },
  "10" : {
    "question" : "Add \\(\\frac {1} {5} + \\frac {3} {4}\\).",
    "answer" : "19/20",
    "solution" : "\\(\\frac {1} {5} + \\frac {3} {4} = \\frac {4} {20} + \\frac {15} {20} = \\frac {19} {20}\\).",
    "explanation" : ""
  }
}

